<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Exammaterials.in</title>
	<atom:link href="http://exammaterials.in/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://exammaterials.in</link>
	<description>Materials for Exams</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 17:03:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://exammaterials.in/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-Logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Exammaterials.in</title>
	<link>https://exammaterials.in</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How important are JEE Main Answer Keys before results to apply for NITs</title>
		<link>https://exammaterials.in/how-important-are-jee-main-answer-keys-before-results-to-apply-for-nits/</link>
					<comments>https://exammaterials.in/how-important-are-jee-main-answer-keys-before-results-to-apply-for-nits/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Guest Article]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 17:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jee mains]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://exammaterials.in/?p=2650</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NITs are autonomous institutes under the Central Government of India for technical and research studies. Previously, NIT was famously known as Regional Engineering College (REC). Through the NIT Act 2007, these were later recognized as Institute of National Importance (INI). There are 31 NITs across India that are listed and are among top-ranked institutes in technology. NITs take admission for their Engineering Courses through JEE Main Exam scores. NTA will release JEE Main Answer Keys tentatively by 2nd week of September after the exams are over. The JEE Main Answer Keys for January session is already released. The Answer Keys…]]></description>
		
					<wfw:commentRss>https://exammaterials.in/how-important-are-jee-main-answer-keys-before-results-to-apply-for-nits/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Steps to Challenge your JEE Main Answer Keys and check latest updates</title>
		<link>https://exammaterials.in/5-steps-to-challenge-your-jee-main-answer-keys-and-check-latest-updates/</link>
					<comments>https://exammaterials.in/5-steps-to-challenge-your-jee-main-answer-keys-and-check-latest-updates/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Guest Article]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 04:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jee mains]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://exammaterials.in/?p=2644</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The class 12th results of many board examinations are already out, and with this, there is the responsibility of the students to sit for entrances and get admission into good colleges. The JEE Main is one of the fundamental examinations of the engineering aspirants to get selected to top colleges for an engineering degree. JEE Main Answer Keys for April Exam will be out tentatively after the exam which will be held between 1st &#8211; 6th September 2020. With so many uncertainties prevailing around the world due to the pandemic of Covid-19, the NTA or National Testing Agency that conducts…]]></description>
		
					<wfw:commentRss>https://exammaterials.in/5-steps-to-challenge-your-jee-main-answer-keys-and-check-latest-updates/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Download Concepts of Physics Part 2 (By HC Verma)</title>
		<link>https://exammaterials.in/concepts-of-physics-hc-varma-part-2/</link>
					<comments>https://exammaterials.in/concepts-of-physics-hc-varma-part-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Srujan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 13:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Physics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://exammaterials.in/?p=2595</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Here you can download Concepts of physics by HC Verma part 1 PDF for free. This book is a gold standard for preparing for IIT JEE. It has all the concepts well explained with examples to get around the concepts. It has the most popular problem in IIT JEE world (The Monkey Problem). For solutions to problems in this book click here (or) Please support the Author by buying the book. An Author spends his valuable time to craft his perfect book to the students to get the most valuable knowledge. Also according to many scientific researches its concluded that…]]></description>
		
					<wfw:commentRss>https://exammaterials.in/concepts-of-physics-hc-varma-part-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Download Concepts of Physics Part 1 (By HC Verma)</title>
		<link>https://exammaterials.in/concepts-of-physics-hc-varma-part-1/</link>
					<comments>https://exammaterials.in/concepts-of-physics-hc-varma-part-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Srujan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Physics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://exammaterials.in/?p=2593</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Here you can download Concepts of physics by HC Verma part 1 PDF for free. This book is a gold standard for preparing for IIT JEE. It has all the concepts well explained with examples to get around the concepts. It has the most popular problem in IIT JEE world (The Monkey Problem). For solutions to problems in this book click here (or) Please support the Author by buying the book. An Author spends his valuable time to craft his perfect book to the students to get the most valuable knowledge. If you like the work of the Author please…]]></description>
		
					<wfw:commentRss>https://exammaterials.in/concepts-of-physics-hc-varma-part-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Comprehensive Mathematics for JEE Advanced (TMH)</title>
		<link>https://exammaterials.in/comprehensive-mathematics-for-jee-advanced-tmh/</link>
					<comments>https://exammaterials.in/comprehensive-mathematics-for-jee-advanced-tmh/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Srujan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 13:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[JEE Advanced]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://exammaterials.in/?p=2570</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Here you can download Comprehensive Mathematics for JEE Advanced PDF for free. Comprehensive Mathematics for JEE Advanced (also famously called as TMH) is a great book for preparation of JEE Advanced. THM Mathematics is one of the most famous books in the JEE world. It is used by many JEE top rankers as per their interviews. This book covers all the Maths syllabus. (or) If you like the book, I strongly recommend to purchase the book to study easy and support the author. The author spends his valuable time in effort to create a best book for students to relay…]]></description>
		
					<wfw:commentRss>https://exammaterials.in/comprehensive-mathematics-for-jee-advanced-tmh/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Download Errorless Chemistry PDF</title>
		<link>https://exammaterials.in/download-errorless-chemistry-pdf/</link>
					<comments>https://exammaterials.in/download-errorless-chemistry-pdf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Srujan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Chemistry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://exammaterials.in/?p=2433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Here you can download Errorless chemistry PDF for free. Errorless Chemistry consist physical, inorganic and organic chemistry for JEE examination. It has good amount of questions to practice and great level of explanation of theory. The quality of the book is at peaks but the only down side of the book is of its price. Check out the PDF in the link below and if you like the content in the book you can purchase risk free. (or) Please consider purchasing the book if you feel the content of the book is good for you to prepare from. This supports…]]></description>
		
					<wfw:commentRss>https://exammaterials.in/download-errorless-chemistry-pdf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Download Digital Logic and Computer Design By M. Morris Mano PDF</title>
		<link>https://exammaterials.in/download-digital-logic-and-computer-design-by-m-morris-mano-pdf/</link>
					<comments>https://exammaterials.in/download-digital-logic-and-computer-design-by-m-morris-mano-pdf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Srujan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 10:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://exammaterials.in/?p=2404</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Here you can download Digital Logic and Computer Design By M. Morris Mano PDF for free. This book presents the basic concepts used in the design and analysis of digital systems and introduces the principles of digital computer organization and design. It discusses various methods and techniques suitable for a variety of digital system design applications and covers all aspects of digital systems. Also this a prescribed book for many universities not only in India but Around the world (or) Buy the original hard copy books from amazon to support the author and for easy preparation. Since this book is…]]></description>
		
					<wfw:commentRss>https://exammaterials.in/download-digital-logic-and-computer-design-by-m-morris-mano-pdf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Download Physical chemistry by Narendra Avasthi PDF</title>
		<link>https://exammaterials.in/download-physical-chemistry-by-narendra-avasthi-pdf/</link>
					<comments>https://exammaterials.in/download-physical-chemistry-by-narendra-avasthi-pdf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Srujan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 10:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://exammaterials.in/?p=2333</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Here you can download Physical chemistry by Narendra Avasthi PDF. This book contains the concept and problems of Physical chemistry. This book is enough for JEE main and advanced. It has 3 levels of problems, Level 1 contains problems for JEE Main and NCERT, and next two levels contains questions for JEE Advanced which includes multi correct, matrix match, paragraph, integer type (also decimal type for some). The difficulty level is also greatly matched (some times the questions are more difficult type than the questions asked in Advanced). The only con is that there are only solutions for selected problems…]]></description>
		
					<wfw:commentRss>https://exammaterials.in/download-physical-chemistry-by-narendra-avasthi-pdf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Download Allen JEE Main Mock test 2020</title>
		<link>https://exammaterials.in/download-allen-jee-main-mock-test-2020/</link>
					<comments>https://exammaterials.in/download-allen-jee-main-mock-test-2020/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Srujan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 12:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[JEE Mains]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://exammaterials.in/?p=2329</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Here you can download Allen Mock test papers for JEE Mains for free. These Mock test helps you to gain confidence in what you prepared and gives you an idea of time management. So always trust the sentence practice makes a man perfect! Allen mock test for JEE main 1 with solution Download PDF Allen mock test for JEE main 2 with Solution Download PDF Allen mock test for JEE main 3 with Solution Download PDF Allen mock test for JEE main 4 with Solution Download PDF Allen Mock Test for JEE Main 5 with Solution Download PDF]]></description>
		
					<wfw:commentRss>https://exammaterials.in/download-allen-jee-main-mock-test-2020/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Download Resonance Mock test for JEE Mains 2020</title>
		<link>https://exammaterials.in/download-resonance-mock-test-for-jee-mains-2020/</link>
					<comments>https://exammaterials.in/download-resonance-mock-test-for-jee-mains-2020/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Srujan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 12:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[JEE Mains]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://exammaterials.in/?p=2325</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Here you can download Resonance Mock test papers for JEE Mains for free. These Mock test helps you to gain confidence in what you prepared and gives you an idea of time management. So always trust the sentence practice makes a man perfect! Mock Test 1 with Solution Download PDF Mock Test 2 with Solution Download PDF Mock Test 3 with Solution Download PDF Mock Test 4 with Solution Download PDF Mock Test 5 with Solution Download PDF Mock Test 6 with Solution Download PDF Mock Test 7 with Solution Download PDF Mock Test 8 with Solution Download PDF Mock…]]></description>
		
					<wfw:commentRss>https://exammaterials.in/download-resonance-mock-test-for-jee-mains-2020/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
